technewsworld.com 2019-05-04

# ECT News Network Privacy Policy

Overview  
This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to modify or correct it. The policies set forth below are applicable to the online media properties and electronic newsletters (collectively referred to herein as "the Service") which are owned and operated by [ECT News Network, Inc](http://www.ectnews.com/). 

Privacy Mission  
ECT News Network is a privacy conscious organization and we are strongly committed to your right to privacy. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. 

Data Collection  
ECT News Network collects personal information from users during registration, and in certain areas of the Service where visitors provide information together with content submissions, postings to online community discussion boards, suggestions, surveys, voting and opinion polling. ECT News Network uses this information for its internal objectives, including but not limited to editorial and feedback purposes. You may be able to access and view portions of the Service without providing personal information, but other areas may require registration for access.

ECT News Network may collect non-personal information, such as information obtained from other sources, or aggregated information that does not identify individual customers. We may also collect the domains and IP addresses of visitors to the Service, as well as information such as browser type and operating system that is generally transmitted by your browser.

Use of Your Information  
Information submitted at the time of registration or content submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by ECT News Network. We may also collect and use information about how our users use the Service, including search terms entered, pages visited and documents viewed. This information is unique-number identifiable, and is used for purposes of enabling us to provide you with a personalized user experience. Aggregated forms of this data may also be used in order to help us understand areas for future research and to identify future features and functions to develop for the Service. This data may also be used by the Service to identify appropriate product offerings and subscription plans. 

The Service and its partners may also use your information:

  * To respond to an inquiry or request for information;
  * To thank you for contacting the Service;
  * To welcome you to the Service and to its products and services;
  * To explain new product offerings and features of our services;
  * To notify you of special promotions;
  * To attribute content you make available through the Service;
  * To communicate with you regarding customer service related issues;
  * For the purposes for which you provided the information; and
  * To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Service, including this privacy policy and our [Terms of Service](http://www.ectnews.com/about/terms-of-service.xhtml).

Registration  
In order to use some features of the Service and to participate in interactive sessions, you will be asked to complete a registration form. During registration, you may be required to provide contact information for yourself and the company you represent -- as well as business information about the company you represent. ECT News Network may use this contact information as a means of confirmation of your identity, position, or relationship to a particular enterprise or company. By using the Service, you agree to reveal only information that you are authorized to disclose and know to be true. During interactive sessions, we may also collect your opinions and preferences regarding certain products or services. We use this information to provide you with quality services as well as with offers that we think are relevant to you based on the preferences you share at registration or during interactive sessions. Please see the Information Sharing and Disclosure section below. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure  
ECT News Network may share certain aggregated demographic information with our sponsors regarding the users of the Service and responses we receive from you via interactive sessions. The aggregated information that we provide does not contain any personally identifiable information. 

ECT News Network may provide authorized access to personal information to employees and others who assist us in providing the Service. In addition, ECT News Network may share personal information with companies that have been approved by ECT News Network so that they can provide you with information about goods and services we believe might interest you. You can opt out of such sharing by [e-mail request](http://www.ectnews.com/perl/contact_form.pl?to=contact) or by modifying your registration information [online](http://www.ectnews.com/perl/User.pl?action=newsletter_settings_html). 

If you have accessed the Service via the Web site of one of our partners, then any information that you provide is provided both to us and to the partner. The partner's use of this information is governed by the partner's privacy policy. You should contact these partners directly if you have any questions about their use of the information. 

ECT News Network may disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our [Terms of Service](http://www.ectnews.com/about/terms-of-service.xhtml), or as otherwise required by law.

In the event ECT News Network is acquired by or merged with another company, we may transfer your information as part of the business transaction.

Special Offers  
As a registered user, and based upon the preferences you chose at registration, you will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers and newsletters. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the [option](http://www.ectnews.com/perl/User.pl?action=newsletter_settings_html) to not receive these types of communications. As part of our services, we may contact you with offers, promotions and information on interactive sessions sponsored by identified third parties. All of the content related to such correspondence is provided by our sponsors, and ECT News Network disclaims any liability for such content. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in promotions. By participating in such promotions, you agree to provide these third parties with your personal information, and further agree that their use of the information is subject to those parties’ own privacy policies. In the event you submit your information in response to a contest or offer provided by ECT News Network in conjunction with one of our partners, that information is provided both to ECT News Network and the partner. 

Cookies  
A cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive that may contain information about you and your use of the Service. ECT News Network utilizes cookies to identify you and your access privileges when using the Service. We also may use cookies to enhance and track usage, and better understand how the Service is used. Cookies do not contain your personally identifiable information.

Users of the Service may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. These cookies are set by the advertisers and are subject to those advertisers’ policies. By using the Service, you expressly agree that the ECT News Network bears no liability whatsoever, for real or perceived privacy invasion, or usage tracking technologies used by third-party ad services which are utilized by various advertisers. You agree that ECT News Network has no control over content served by third-party ad services, and that any remedies must be sought solely against those services. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. The "Help" section of the toolbar on most browsers will describe how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. However, if you do not accept cookies from a domain owned by ECT News Network, it is possible that the Service will not function properly for you at all times. 

Links to Other Web Sites  
ECT News Network may provide links to other Web sites for your convenience and information. ECT News Network is not responsible for the privacy procedures of these other sites. The entities that operate these sites are responsible for the content of their sites, any products or services they may offer through their sites, or any other use of their sites. Other Web sites may have their own privacy notices in place, which we recommend you review if you visit them as a result of your use of the Service. 

Security  
ECT News Network maintains reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards to defend against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration or destruction of the personal information in our possession. 

Visiting Our Websites from Outside the United States  
This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our websites from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

Privacy of Children  
ECT News Network and the Services it provides are not directed to children under the age of 13. The Service operates in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and we do not knowingly accept registration by, and will not intentionally collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age. In the event that we learn that we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database. 

How to Change User Information  
You may update or correct information you previously provided to ECT News Network by accessing your [user profile](http://www.ectnews.com/perl/User.pl). If you have any questions or concerns about the ECT News Network privacy policy or would like the personally identifiable information that you have provided to ECT News Network removed from our files, please [contact us](http://www.ectnews.com/about/#contact). 

Your California Privacy Rights  
If you are a California resident, you are entitled by law to request an Information Sharing Disclosure. If you provide notice to the address below, ECT News Network will provide you with a notice of your right to prevent sharing of your personal information as well as a cost-free means of doing so. To receive such a notice, submit a written request to our Reader Services Department, specifying that you seek your "California Customer Choice Notice." Please allow thirty days for response.

Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy  
We may change or update portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. We suggest that you check this page periodically so you are aware of any policy changes or updates. We will indicate above the effective date of the update or change.

Governing Law  
This policy and the use of this Service are governed by California law. Any claim related to the Service or this policy shall be brought in a federal or state court in Los Angeles County, California, within one year after the claim arises. You consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such court as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this policy.

Contacting Us  
If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at:

Attn: Reader Services  
ECT News Network, Inc.  
PO Box 18500  
Encino, CA 91416-8500
